playquiz2win.com 2016-11-06

# Privacy Policy | Playquiz2win

_You are here:_ [_Home_](http://www.playquiz2win.com/index.html) >> Privacy

### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which playquiz2win collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the [http://www.playquiz2win.com](http://www.playquiz2win.com/) website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by playquiz2win.com

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, phone number. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

##### Viewing ads of your choice

Google AdSense is world’s largest , most prestigious and transparent advertising company. The Ads presented on the site are non obtrusive and don’t affect your computer adversely. AdSense can also show show you relevant ads based on your interests. By visiting [this link](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/about.html) you can add your interests so that Google shows you ads based upon your interest, while browsing internet.

#####  About Cookies & Web Beacons:

Cookies and web beacons are used by these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) to collect information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This does not include your email address, mobile numbers etc. This _is used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York and showing India specific ads to somebody in India at the same time ” ), so You don’t need to worry about it._

##### What is a Cookie?

A cookie is a small text file containing a string of characters that a website sends your computer. It records information necessary for certain website functions, such as remembering your preferences or settings. _A cookie will not allow us or any third-party to learn any personally identifiable information that you have not otherwise disclosed._

##### Do All the Major Sites Use Cookies?

The use of cookies is an industry standard, and they are currently used on most major websites. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you change your browser’s cookie settings to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Some features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

##### What is a Web Beacon?

Web beacons are small strings of HTML code that are placed in a Web page. They are sometimes called “clear GIFs” (Graphics Interchange Format) or “pixel tags.” Web beacons are most often used in conjunction with cookies. DoubleClick uses Web beacons in connection with its products and services, including [ad serving](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx#adserving) and paid search listings (“DART Search”). Because a Web beacon is only 1 pixel high by 1 pixel wide, it appears invisible on your computer screen.

##### What are DoubleClick DART cookies:

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. _However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites_. This could include the inability to log in to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

**How we use collected information**  
playquiz2win may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _\- To improve customer service_  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * _\- To personalize user experience_  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * _\- To improve our Site_  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * _\- To send periodic emails_  
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, they may do so by contacting us via our Site.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Our Site is in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Playquiz2win has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
**contact@playquiz2win.com, and  
sonunetin6@gmail.com**   
This document was last updated on June 14, 2015
